{"data":[{"question":"A group of ___ are eating grass at the foot of the hill.","a":"cattle","b":"catties","c":"cattlees","d":"cattleies","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"Cattle\" is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The monitor will hand out the Chemistry ___ after class.","a":"examination's papers","b":"paper for examination","c":"papers of examination","d":"examination papers","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) \n+ Examination papers: papers used in examination (stress on paper) \n+ Examination's papers: papers of examination (stress on examination) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"There were much more ___ in our school than in yours.","a":"male's teachers","b":"male teacher's","c":"male's teacher's","d":"male teachers","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) \n+ Male teachers: Teachers who are males","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Our teacher gave us ___ on how to improve our Mandarin.","a":"several advices","b":"an advice","c":"a piece advice","d":"some advice","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Advice is an uncountable noun. This means that we can't say an advice. Instead, we say some advice or a piece of advice\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Darwin didn't mean to attack people's religious ___.","a":"beliefs","b":"belief","c":"believs","d":"believes","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Belief (countable): an idea that you believe to be true, especially one that forms part of a system of ideas\n\n- Belief -> (plural) beliefs","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The poor little girl had lots of ___ to do every day.","a":"homeworks","b":"houseworks","c":"jobs","d":"works","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Job (countable): a particular thing you have to do, considered as work\n\n- Homework, housework, work: uncountable noun-> no \"s\" in plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Several ___ are waiting for you outside.","a":"American","b":"Germen","c":"Japanese","d":"grown-up","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Japanese = Japanese people","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The hunter ran to a group of _________ with two","a":"wolves, knives","b":"wolfs, knives","c":"wolves, knifes","d":"wolfs, knifes","answer":"1","explain":".","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"My mom bought some ___ in the supermarket yesterday.","a":"potatos","b":"tomatoes","c":"Meats","d":"vegetable","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tomato (countable):- (plural) +es \n- Potato (countable)- (plural)+ es \n- Meat: uncoutable- (plural) no\"s\" \n- Vegetable: (countable)- (plural) + s","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"That lady asked the shopkeeper what the ___ of the phone was.","a":"money","b":"costs","c":"price","d":"value","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Price: the amount of money you have to pay for something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}